{
    "translations": {
      "en": {
        "fa1": "../../../AV/VisFormalLang/NFA/AutomataFiles/NFA2DFA2a.jff",
        "q1": {
          "type": "select",
          "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
          "question":"Which of the following are  alphabet sets?",
          "answer": ["{a, b, c}", "{0, 1}", "{?, a, x}"],
          "choices": ["{a, b, c}", "{0, 1}","A" ,"{?, a, x}"]
        },
        "q2": {
          "type": "select",
          "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
          "question":"Suppose we have Σ = {a, b}, which of the following are valid strings?",
          "answer": ["babababbaba", "a"],
          "choices": ["babababbaba", "a","{aaa, bbb}", "bacbabcba" ]
        },
        "q3": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"What states can be combined?",
          "answer": ["Σ={0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, 9} L={0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,...}", 
            "Σ={a,b,c} L={ab,ac,cabb}",
            "Σ={0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, 9} L={set of all even numbers}" ],
          "choices": ["Σ={0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, 9} L={0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,...}", 
            "Σ={a,b,c} L={ab,ac,cabb}",
            "Σ={0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, 9} L={set of all even numbers}" ]
        },
        "q4":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"List the power set of {a, b}",
          "answer": ["a"],
          "choices": ["a", "b", "a, b"]
        },
        "q5":{
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"So, when you see b in a sentence, it probably refers to:",
          "answer": "The character ‘b’.",
          "choices": ["The character ‘b’.", "Some string named ‘b’."]
        },
        "q5_1":{
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"And if y see w in a sentence, it probably refers to ",
          "answer":"Some string given the name ‘w’",
          "choices": ["The character ‘w’", "Some string given the name ‘w’"]
        },
        "q6":{
          "type": "fill in blank",
          "question":"Let w=abbc, v=ab, What is |w| + |v|",
          "answer":"6"
        },
        "q7":{
          "type": "select",
          "question": "Let w = abc, v = 012, What is w∘v?",
          "answer":"abc012",
          "choices": ["abc012"]
        },
        "q8":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"let v = ab, what is v3 ?",
          "answer": ["vvv", "v∘v∘v", "ababab"],
          "choices": ["vvv", "v∘v∘v", "ababab"]
        },
        "q8_1":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Is this a language? {λ}",
          "answer":"yes",
          "choices": ["yes"]
        },
        "q9":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"What is λ∘acb∘λ?",
          "answer":"acb",
          "choices": ["acb"]
        },
        "q10":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Let w = abbc, what is wR?",
          "answer":"cbba",
          "choices": ["cbba"]
        },
        "q11":{
          "type": "fill in a blank",
          "question":"let w=abbc, and v=ab. What is |vvRw|",
          "answer":"8"
        },
        "q12":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Which of the following are strings in Σ∗?",
          "answer":["λ", "a", "b", "aa", "abbabb"],
          "choices": ["λ", "a", "b", "aa", "abbabb", "aaabababcc"]
        },
        "q12_1":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Which are examples of w* where w = abc?",
          "answer":["Λ", "abc", "abcabc"],
          "choices": ["Λ", "abc", "abcabc", "aabbcc"]
        },
        "q13":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Let  Σ = {a,b}, Which of the following are strings in Σ∗?",
          "answer":  ["a", "b", "aa", "abbabb"],
          "choices": ["λ", "a", "b", "aa", "abbabb", "aaabababcc"]
        },
        "q14":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":" Let Σ={a,b,c}, L1={ab,bc,aba}, L2={c,bc,bcc}, What is L1∪L2 ?",
          "answer":"{ab,bc,aba,c,bcc}",
          "choices": ["{ab,bc,aba,c,bcc}"]

        },
        "q15":{
          "type": "fill in blank",
          "question":"Let Σ={a,b,c}, L1={ab,bc,aba}, L2={c,bc,bcc}, What is L1∩L2 ?",
          "answer":"{bc}",
          "choices": ["{bc}"]
        },
        "q16":{
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is ?",
          "answer":" " ,
          "choices": [" "]
        },
        "q17":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"What states can be combined?",
          "answer":"{abc,abbc,abbcc,bcc,bcbc,bcbcc,abac,ababc,ababcc}",
          "choices":["{abc,abbc,abbcc,bcc,bcbc,bcbcc,abac,ababc,ababcc}"]
        },
        "q18":{
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"Let Σ={a,b}, L1={ab,aba}, What is L0?",
          "answer":"{λ}",
          "choices": ["{λ}", "{}<Empty set>", "λ"]
        },
        "q19":{
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Let Σ={a,b}, L1={ab,aba}, What is L2? ",
          "answer":"{abab, ababa, abaab, abaaba}" ,
          "choices": ["{abab, ababa, abaab, abaaba}"]
        },
        "q19_1":{
          "type": "fill in blank",
          "question":"Let Σ={a,b}, L1={ab,aba}, What is L3?",
          "answer":"{ababab, ababaab, abaabab, abaabaab, abababa, ababaaba, abaababa, abaabaaba}" ,
          "choices": ["{ababab, ababaab, abaabab, abaabaab, abababa, ababaaba, abaababa, abaabaaba}"]
        }
      }
    }
  }
  